[
	{
		"question": "Click on the number zero!",
		"answer": "0",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number zero"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number one!",
		"answer": "1",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number one"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number two!",
		"answer": "2",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number two"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number three!",
		"answer": "3",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number three"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number four!",
		"answer": "4",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number four"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number five!",
		"answer": "5",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number five"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number six!",
		"answer": "6",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number six"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number seven!",
		"answer": "7",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number seven"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number eight!",
		"answer": "8",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number eight"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number nine!",
		"answer": "9",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number nine"
	},
	{
		"question": "Click on the number ten!",
		"answer": "10",
		"prompt": "No, this is the number ten"
	}
]